♪♪ Lately I've been hard to reach ♪♪
♪♪ I've been too long on my own ♪♪
♪♪ Everybody has a private world ♪♪
♪♪ Where they can be alone ♪♪
♪♪ Are you calling me? ♪♪
♪♪ Are you trying to get through ♪♪
♪♪ Are you reaching out for me ♪♪
♪♪ Like I'm reaching out for you? ♪♪
♪♪ I'm just so fucking depressed ♪♪
♪♪ I just can't seem to get out this slump ♪♪
♪♪ If I could just get over this hump ♪♪
♪♪ But I need somethin' to pull me out this dump ♪♪
♪♪ I took my bruises, took my lumps ♪♪
♪♪ Fell down and I got right back up ♪♪
♪♪ But I need that spark to get psyched back up ♪♪
♪♪ In order for me to pick the mic back up ♪♪
♪♪ I don't know how or why or when ♪♪
♪♪ I ended up in this position I'm in ♪♪
♪♪ I'm starting to feel distant again ♪♪
♪♪ So I decided just to pick this pen ♪♪
♪♪ Up and try to make an attempt to vent ♪♪
♪♪ But I just can't admit or come to grips with the fact ♪♪
♪♪ That I may be done with rap, I need a new outlet ♪♪
♪♪ And I know some shit's so hard to swallow ♪♪
♪♪ But I just can't sit back and wallow ♪♪
♪♪ In my own sorrow, but I know one fact ♪♪
♪♪ I'll be one tough act to follow ♪♪
♪♪ one tough act to follow ♪♪
♪♪ Here today, gone tomorrow ♪♪
♪♪ But you'd have to walk a thousand miles— ♪♪
♪♪ In my shoes, just to see what it's like to be me ♪♪
♪♪ I'll be you, let's trade shoes ♪♪
♪♪ Just to see what it'd be like to ♪♪
♪♪ Feel your pain, you feel mine ♪♪
♪♪ Go inside each other's minds ♪♪
♪♪ Just to see what we find ♪♪
♪♪ Look at shit through each other's eyes ♪♪
♪♪ But don't let 'em say you ain't beautiful ♪♪
♪♪ Woah-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ They can all get fucked, just stay true to you ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Don't let 'em say you ain't beautiful ♪♪
♪♪ Ho-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ They can all get fucked, just stay true to you ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ I think I'm starting to lose my sense of humor ♪♪
♪♪ Everything's so tense and gloom ♪♪
♪♪ I almost feel like I gotta check the temperature ♪♪
♪♪ Of the room, just as soon as ♪♪
♪♪ I walk in, it's like all eyes on me ♪♪
♪♪ So I try to avoid any eye contact ♪♪
♪♪ ‘Cause if I do that, then it opens a door ♪♪
♪♪ For conversation like I want that ♪♪
♪♪ I'm not lookin' for extra attention ♪♪
♪♪ I just wanna be just like you ♪♪
♪♪ Blend in with the rest of the room ♪♪
♪♪ Maybe just point me to the closest restroom ♪♪
♪♪ I don't need no fucking man servant ♪♪
♪♪ Trying to follow me around and wipe my ass ♪♪
♪♪ Laugh at every single joke I crack ♪♪
♪♪ And half of 'em ain't even funny, like, ha ♪♪
♪♪ Marshall, you're so funny, man ♪♪
♪♪ You should be a comedian, goddamn! ♪♪
♪♪ Unfortunately I am ♪♪
♪♪ I just hide behind the tears of a clown ♪♪
♪♪ So why don't you all sit down ♪♪
♪♪ Listen to the tale I'm about to tell ♪♪
♪♪ Hell, we don't gotta trade our shoes ♪♪
♪♪ And you ain't gotta walk no thousand miles— ♪♪
♪♪ In my shoes, just to see what it's like to be me ♪♪
♪♪ I'll be you, let's trade shoes ♪♪
♪♪ Just to see what it'd be like to ♪♪
♪♪ Feel your pain, you feel mine ♪♪
♪♪ Go inside each other's minds ♪♪
♪♪ Just to see what we find ♪♪
♪♪ Look at shit through each other's eyes ♪♪
♪♪ But don't let 'em say you ain't beautiful ♪♪
♪♪ Ho-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ They can all get fucked, just stay true to you ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Don't let 'em say you ain't beautiful ♪♪
♪♪ Ho-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ They can all get fucked, just stay true to you ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Nobody asked for life to deal us ♪♪
♪♪ With these bullshit hands we're dealt ♪♪
♪♪ We gotta take these cards ourselves ♪♪
♪♪ And flip 'em, don't expect no help ♪♪
♪♪ Now, I could've either just sat on my ass ♪♪
♪♪ And pissed and moaned ♪♪
♪♪ Or take this situation in which I'm placed in ♪♪
♪♪ And get up and get my own ♪♪
♪♪ I was never the type of kid ♪♪
♪♪ To wait by the door and pack his bags ♪♪
♪♪ And sat on the porch and hoped and prayed ♪♪
♪♪ For a dad to show up who never did ♪♪
♪♪ I just wanted to fit in in every single place ♪♪
♪♪ Every school I went ♪♪
♪♪ I dreamed of being that cool kid ♪♪
♪♪ Even if it meant acting stupid ♪♪
♪♪ Aunt Edna always told me ♪♪
♪♪ Keep making that face, it'll get stuck like that ♪♪
♪♪ Meanwhile, I'm just standin' there ♪♪
♪♪ Holdin' my tongue, tryin' to talk *like this* ♪♪
♪♪ 'Til I stuck my tongue on that frozen stop sign pole ♪♪
♪♪ At eight years old; I learned my lesson then ♪♪
♪♪ ‘Cause I wasn't tryin' to impress my friends no more ♪♪
♪♪ But I already told you my whole life story ♪♪
♪♪ Not just based on my description ♪♪
♪♪ ‘Cause where you see it from where you're sittin' ♪♪
♪♪ It's probably 110% different ♪♪
♪♪ I guess we would have to walk a mile ♪♪
♪♪ In each other's shoes at least ♪♪
♪♪ What size you wear? ♪♪
♪♪ I wear 10's ♪♪
♪♪ Let's see if you can fit your feet— ♪♪
♪♪ In my shoes, just to see what it's like to be me ♪♪
♪♪ I'll be you, let's trade shoes ♪♪
♪♪ Just to see what it'd be like to ♪♪
♪♪ Feel your pain, you feel mine ♪♪
♪♪ Go inside each other's minds ♪♪
♪♪ Just to see what we find ♪♪
♪♪ Look at shit through each other's eyes ♪♪
♪♪ But don't let 'em say you ain't beautiful ♪♪
♪♪ Ho-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ They can all get fucked, just stay true to you ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Don't let 'em say you ain't beautiful ♪♪
♪♪ Ho-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ They can all get fucked, just stay true to you ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Lately I've been hard to reach ♪♪
♪♪ I've been too long on my own ♪♪
♪♪ Oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Everybody has a private world ♪♪
♪♪ Where they can be alone ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Are you calling me? ♪♪
♪♪ Are you trying to get through ♪♪
♪♪ Whoa-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Are you reaching out for me ♪♪
♪♪ Like I'm reaching out for you? ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪
♪♪ Yeah, to my babies, stay strong ♪♪
♪♪ Daddy'll be home soon ♪♪
♪♪ And to the rest of the world ♪♪
♪♪ God gave you them shoes to fit you ♪♪
♪♪ So put 'em on and wear 'em ♪♪
♪♪ Be yourself, man, be proud of who you are ♪♪
♪♪ Even if it sounds corny ♪♪
♪♪ Don't ever let anyone tell you ♪♪
♪♪ You ain't beautiful ♪♪
♪♪ So-oh-oh-oh-ohh ♪♪